<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crime on silas mcnutt</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/tags/crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crime on silas mcnutt</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:03:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/tags/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Class Action Park (2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/class-action-park-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:03:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/class-action-park-2020/</guid>
      <description>Class Action Park (2020) - Link to heading&#xD;There ain’t nothing like the 80s!&#xA;Hearing about Action Park is one of those things that makes you go “how the hell did that ever happen?” and then you remember that this was the 80s where you could blow up an entire building and no one would do much besides laugh. Class Action Park does a pretty solid job of documenting some of the history surrounding the park and its questionable attractions and shady business practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Grand Budapest Hotel (2014)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-grand-budapest-hotel-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:50:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-grand-budapest-hotel-2014/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Budapest Hotel (2014) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Boy am I a slut for Wes Anderson films, and boy did The Grand Budapest Hotel not disappoint. This movie is paced extremely well. It’s light-hearted, but melancholic. It’s funny, but packs a serious punch. It has everything you’d want from a movie and more. The first thing I wanted to do after I watched this movie was watch it again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Righteous Kill (2008)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/righteous-kill-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 03:45:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/righteous-kill-2008/</guid>
      <description>Righteous Kill (2008) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;To be honest, I feel like everyone is a little tough on Righteous Kill. Was the movie great? No. But dropping 0.5 or 1 star ratings on this bad boy like it&amp;rsquo;s Diary of A Wimpy Kid: The Long Haul is just an outright crime. Look, I get it. Throwing De Niro and Pacino into a film together and it coming out undercooked is something that saddens me as well, but to act like this movie had nothing to take off on is just harsh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: 12 Angry Men (1957)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/12-angry-men-1957/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:02:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/12-angry-men-1957/</guid>
      <description>12 Angry Men (1957) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Quick sidenote: I had writer’s block as I wrote nearly this entire review so apologies in advance. It’s not very good and I certainly don’t do the movie justice.&#xA;Spoiler-Free Section Man, they don’t make movies like they used to. I don’t think I’ve ever come across a film with better writing than 12 Angry Men. The comedic aspects, the dramatic irony, and smart remarks make every piece of dialogue so enjoyable in their own respective ways.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
