<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drama on silas mcnutt</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/tags/drama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drama on silas mcnutt</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:05:15 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/tags/drama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Fall Guy (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-fall-guy-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:05:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-fall-guy-2024/</guid>
      <description>The Fall Guy (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;“I’m on Metalstorm, too!” “Liar! We’re on Metalstorm ONE!”&#xA;I’ll be honest, I’m not sure why I held off on this movie for so long. When it came out it looked fun, but not fun enough for me to go out of my way to watch. When I started looking for movies to watch, I wanted something released this year because I felt like there were a few that I had missed out on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Inside Out 2 (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/inside-out-2-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:30:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/inside-out-2-2024/</guid>
      <description>Inside Out 2 (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;I think it’s fair to say that this is one of the better Pixar films in recent history. Inside Out 2 was shockingly good, and I loved every minute of it. The pacing, the animation, the plot, the morals, and everything in between was fantastic. Dare I say that this was better than the first? Seriously though, I came out feeling as if there was so much more to take away than anything the first one had begun to touch on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: On the Rocks (2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/on-the-rocks-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:04:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/on-the-rocks-2020/</guid>
      <description>On the Rocks (2020) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;While there isn’t much to say about this lovely little flick, it’s nice to have a watch with movies like these every now and then. On The Rocks is a nice little changeup from your run of the mill romance movie, with Laura questioning the legitimacy of her marriage, leading to an all out investigation on her husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: 12 Angry Men (1957)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/12-angry-men-1957/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:02:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/12-angry-men-1957/</guid>
      <description>12 Angry Men (1957) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Quick sidenote: I had writer’s block as I wrote nearly this entire review so apologies in advance. It’s not very good and I certainly don’t do the movie justice.&#xA;Spoiler-Free Section Man, they don’t make movies like they used to. I don’t think I’ve ever come across a film with better writing than 12 Angry Men. The comedic aspects, the dramatic irony, and smart remarks make every piece of dialogue so enjoyable in their own respective ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Robot Dreams (2023)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/robot-dreams-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:48:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/robot-dreams-2023/</guid>
      <description>Robot Dreams (2023) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;My girlfriend and I found this movie by accident when searching for something to watch. Neither of us had heard anything about it, but it quickly drew us in with the cutesy animation and fun feel to it. But boy was I wrong for thinking this would be a happy go lucky type of movie to end the night with.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
