<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Posts on silas mcnutt</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog Posts on silas mcnutt</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:57:09 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Nemesis (1992)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/nemesis-1992/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:57:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/nemesis-1992/</guid>
      <description>Nemesis (1992) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Ok, am I missing something, or was this movie just hot garbage? What is there to like about Nemesis? Shitty writing and acting, cheesy costumes and props, outdated effects, and a plot which is just downright boring make this seem like a student film that got the budget of a B-tier film in the 70s. Let’s go one by one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: 12 Angry Men (1957)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/12-angry-men-1957/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:02:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/12-angry-men-1957/</guid>
      <description>12 Angry Men (1957) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Quick sidenote: I had writer’s block as I wrote nearly this entire review so apologies in advance. It’s not very good and I certainly don’t do the movie justice.&#xA;Spoiler-Free Section Man, they don’t make movies like they used to. I don’t think I’ve ever come across a film with better writing than 12 Angry Men. The comedic aspects, the dramatic irony, and smart remarks make every piece of dialogue so enjoyable in their own respective ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Thing (1982)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-thing-1982/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 01:06:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-thing-1982/</guid>
      <description>The Thing (1982) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Where do I even begin with this movie? The Thing was fantastic. I had high expectations going in, knowing the reputation this film has built for itself, and it didn’t disappoint. This is a true horror film. It doesn’t rely on cheap jumpscares or poor decision making by the characters. The Thing is something that can be beat, albeit not easily, which makes the ending not nearly as predictable as some other horror films where the antagonist is quite literally immortal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Robot Dreams (2023)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/robot-dreams-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:48:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/robot-dreams-2023/</guid>
      <description>Robot Dreams (2023) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;My girlfriend and I found this movie by accident when searching for something to watch. Neither of us had heard anything about it, but it quickly drew us in with the cutesy animation and fun feel to it. But boy was I wrong for thinking this would be a happy go lucky type of movie to end the night with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Madame Web (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/madame-web-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/madame-web-2024/</guid>
      <description>Madame Web (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;This movie was bad. Like, really bad. It sucks because on paper it seems like it would be average, but somehow the writers managed to completely drop the ball. My biggest problem with the entire thing is the forced dialogue. I don’t think there was a single sentence in this entire movie that I felt seemed natural and human.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Garfield Movie (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-garfield-movie-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-garfield-movie-2024/</guid>
      <description>The Garfield Movie (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;This movie drags. And drags, and drags, and drags. About half way through the movie my girlfriend told me she was feeling sick, and from that moment forward I began hoping she would ask to leave just so we could be done with this shitfest of a film. Besides the boring voice acting from Chris Pratt, the mediocre animation, and the extremely lame characters (besides Odie), the plot was also just not fun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Abigail (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/abigail-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/abigail-2024/</guid>
      <description>Abigail (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Spoiler-Free Section&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;I had mediocre expectations going into this movie as I think practically every horror movie is overdone and ends up being a bust, but Abigail was a pleasant surprise. This movie is decently well paced, well acted, and has fine shots. The special effects weren’t great by any stretch of the imagination, but that seems to be a common theme in newer movies with tighter deadlines requiring effects artists to rush.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
