<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Posts on silas mcnutt</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog Posts on silas mcnutt</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:39:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Movie Montage - August 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/monthly-movie-montage-august-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:39:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/monthly-movie-montage-august-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xD;This Month&#39;s Movies&#xD;This Month&#39;s Movies&#xD;Longlegs (2024)&#xD;Selling your soul to the devil has never been worth it, but Longlegs puts into perspective just how horrible it may be with this psychologically thrilling, anxiety inducing movie. Fantastic acting, solid plot, and some beautiful shots land this a very deserving 8/10.&#xA;8&#xD;/&#xD;10&#xD;La La Land (2016)&#xD;Ok, who the hell put crack in this movie? I genuinely could have never guessed that this romance musical would shoot its way up to the top of my rankings and become one of my all time favorites, even with all of the things I had heard long before watching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whats Happening - August 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/whats-happening-august-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:02:13 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/whats-happening-august-2024/</guid>
      <description>Hey all! 👋&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit since I&amp;rsquo;ve posted on my blog, as you&amp;rsquo;ve probably been able to tell. There&amp;rsquo;s a couple of reasons for this. Firstly, I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling a bit and haven&amp;rsquo;t had as much time to focus on write-ups for all of the movies I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching. Second, when I have had downtime, I&amp;rsquo;ve been hard at work on a couple of other projects, which I won&amp;rsquo;t get into too much detail about right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Fall Guy (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-fall-guy-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:05:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-fall-guy-2024/</guid>
      <description>The Fall Guy (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;“I’m on Metalstorm, too!” “Liar! We’re on Metalstorm ONE!”&#xA;I’ll be honest, I’m not sure why I held off on this movie for so long. When it came out it looked fun, but not fun enough for me to go out of my way to watch. When I started looking for movies to watch, I wanted something released this year because I felt like there were a few that I had missed out on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Despicable Me 4 (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/despicable-me-4-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:18:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/despicable-me-4-2024/</guid>
      <description>Despicable Me 4 (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;“I tranqued myself!”&#xA;There’s a reason that Minions: Rise of Gru is the highest rated Despicable Me related movie after the original. Everyone loves the minions! To be honest, though, this franchise is getting worn out. I don’t think that there was anything about this movie that made it stand out from the rest. It was silly and fun, but outside of that there really isn’t much to talk about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Inside Out 2 (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/inside-out-2-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:30:23 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/inside-out-2-2024/</guid>
      <description>Inside Out 2 (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;I think it’s fair to say that this is one of the better Pixar films in recent history. Inside Out 2 was shockingly good, and I loved every minute of it. The pacing, the animation, the plot, the morals, and everything in between was fantastic. Dare I say that this was better than the first? Seriously though, I came out feeling as if there was so much more to take away than anything the first one had begun to touch on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Class Action Park (2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/class-action-park-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:03:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/class-action-park-2020/</guid>
      <description>Class Action Park (2020) - Link to heading&#xD;There ain’t nothing like the 80s!&#xA;Hearing about Action Park is one of those things that makes you go “how the hell did that ever happen?” and then you remember that this was the 80s where you could blow up an entire building and no one would do much besides laugh. Class Action Park does a pretty solid job of documenting some of the history surrounding the park and its questionable attractions and shady business practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Grand Budapest Hotel (2014)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-grand-budapest-hotel-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 03:50:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-grand-budapest-hotel-2014/</guid>
      <description>The Grand Budapest Hotel (2014) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Boy am I a slut for Wes Anderson films, and boy did The Grand Budapest Hotel not disappoint. This movie is paced extremely well. It’s light-hearted, but melancholic. It’s funny, but packs a serious punch. It has everything you’d want from a movie and more. The first thing I wanted to do after I watched this movie was watch it again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Righteous Kill (2008)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/righteous-kill-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 03:45:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/righteous-kill-2008/</guid>
      <description>Righteous Kill (2008) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;To be honest, I feel like everyone is a little tough on Righteous Kill. Was the movie great? No. But dropping 0.5 or 1 star ratings on this bad boy like it&amp;rsquo;s Diary of A Wimpy Kid: The Long Haul is just an outright crime. Look, I get it. Throwing De Niro and Pacino into a film together and it coming out undercooked is something that saddens me as well, but to act like this movie had nothing to take off on is just harsh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: On the Rocks (2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/on-the-rocks-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:04:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/on-the-rocks-2020/</guid>
      <description>On the Rocks (2020) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;While there isn’t much to say about this lovely little flick, it’s nice to have a watch with movies like these every now and then. On The Rocks is a nice little changeup from your run of the mill romance movie, with Laura questioning the legitimacy of her marriage, leading to an all out investigation on her husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Nemesis (1992)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/nemesis-1992/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:57:09 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/nemesis-1992/</guid>
      <description>Nemesis (1992) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Ok, am I missing something, or was this movie just hot garbage? What is there to like about Nemesis? Shitty writing and acting, cheesy costumes and props, outdated effects, and a plot which is just downright boring make this seem like a student film that got the budget of a B-tier film in the 70s. Let’s go one by one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: 12 Angry Men (1957)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/12-angry-men-1957/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:02:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/12-angry-men-1957/</guid>
      <description>12 Angry Men (1957) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Quick sidenote: I had writer’s block as I wrote nearly this entire review so apologies in advance. It’s not very good and I certainly don’t do the movie justice.&#xA;Spoiler-Free Section Man, they don’t make movies like they used to. I don’t think I’ve ever come across a film with better writing than 12 Angry Men. The comedic aspects, the dramatic irony, and smart remarks make every piece of dialogue so enjoyable in their own respective ways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Thing (1982)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-thing-1982/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 01:06:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-thing-1982/</guid>
      <description>The Thing (1982) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Where do I even begin with this movie? The Thing was fantastic. I had high expectations going in, knowing the reputation this film has built for itself, and it didn’t disappoint. This is a true horror film. It doesn’t rely on cheap jumpscares or poor decision making by the characters. The Thing is something that can be beat, albeit not easily, which makes the ending not nearly as predictable as some other horror films where the antagonist is quite literally immortal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Robot Dreams (2023)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/robot-dreams-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:48:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/robot-dreams-2023/</guid>
      <description>Robot Dreams (2023) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;My girlfriend and I found this movie by accident when searching for something to watch. Neither of us had heard anything about it, but it quickly drew us in with the cutesy animation and fun feel to it. But boy was I wrong for thinking this would be a happy go lucky type of movie to end the night with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Madame Web (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/madame-web-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/madame-web-2024/</guid>
      <description>Madame Web (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;This movie was bad. Like, really bad. It sucks because on paper it seems like it would be average, but somehow the writers managed to completely drop the ball. My biggest problem with the entire thing is the forced dialogue. I don’t think there was a single sentence in this entire movie that I felt seemed natural and human.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Garfield Movie (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-garfield-movie-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-garfield-movie-2024/</guid>
      <description>The Garfield Movie (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;This movie drags. And drags, and drags, and drags. About half way through the movie my girlfriend told me she was feeling sick, and from that moment forward I began hoping she would ask to leave just so we could be done with this shitfest of a film. Besides the boring voice acting from Chris Pratt, the mediocre animation, and the extremely lame characters (besides Odie), the plot was also just not fun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Abigail (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/abigail-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/abigail-2024/</guid>
      <description>Abigail (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;Spoiler-Free Section&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;I had mediocre expectations going into this movie as I think practically every horror movie is overdone and ends up being a bust, but Abigail was a pleasant surprise. This movie is decently well paced, well acted, and has fine shots. The special effects weren’t great by any stretch of the imagination, but that seems to be a common theme in newer movies with tighter deadlines requiring effects artists to rush.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
