<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2.5 ★ on silas mcnutt</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/tags/2.5-/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2.5 ★ on silas mcnutt</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:18:44 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/tags/2.5-/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Despicable Me 4 (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/despicable-me-4-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:18:44 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/despicable-me-4-2024/</guid>
      <description>Despicable Me 4 (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;“I tranqued myself!”&#xA;There’s a reason that Minions: Rise of Gru is the highest rated Despicable Me related movie after the original. Everyone loves the minions! To be honest, though, this franchise is getting worn out. I don’t think that there was anything about this movie that made it stand out from the rest. It was silly and fun, but outside of that there really isn’t much to talk about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: Righteous Kill (2008)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/righteous-kill-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 03:45:06 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/righteous-kill-2008/</guid>
      <description>Righteous Kill (2008) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;To be honest, I feel like everyone is a little tough on Righteous Kill. Was the movie great? No. But dropping 0.5 or 1 star ratings on this bad boy like it&amp;rsquo;s Diary of A Wimpy Kid: The Long Haul is just an outright crime. Look, I get it. Throwing De Niro and Pacino into a film together and it coming out undercooked is something that saddens me as well, but to act like this movie had nothing to take off on is just harsh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: On the Rocks (2020)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/on-the-rocks-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:04:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/on-the-rocks-2020/</guid>
      <description>On the Rocks (2020) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;While there isn’t much to say about this lovely little flick, it’s nice to have a watch with movies like these every now and then. On The Rocks is a nice little changeup from your run of the mill romance movie, with Laura questioning the legitimacy of her marriage, leading to an all out investigation on her husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review: The Garfield Movie (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-garfield-movie-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/silasmcnutt.com/posts/posts/the-garfield-movie-2024/</guid>
      <description>The Garfield Movie (2024) - Link to heading&#xD;Follow me on Letterboxd!&#xD;This movie drags. And drags, and drags, and drags. About half way through the movie my girlfriend told me she was feeling sick, and from that moment forward I began hoping she would ask to leave just so we could be done with this shitfest of a film. Besides the boring voice acting from Chris Pratt, the mediocre animation, and the extremely lame characters (besides Odie), the plot was also just not fun.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
